Guide to the Northcutt Ely Papers, 1900-1982
Department of Special Collections
- Series 2. General Subject files
  - Subseries 3. Colorado River
    - Sub-subseries 10. Mexican Water Treaty
      - The 6 States Committee, Vol. 1 - Brief In Support of the Ratification of the Treaty with Mexico Relating to the Utilization of the Waters of Certain Rivers, Accession no. M0223 (Box 76, Folder 4)
      - The 6 States Committee, Vol. 2 - EngineeningMemorandum on the Treaty with Mexico Relating to the Utilization of the Waters of Certain Rivers, Accession no. M0223 (Box 76, Folder 4)
      - The 6 States Committee, Vol. 3 - Appendix and Index - Texts of the Compacts, Contracts and Treaties, Accession no. M0223 (Box 76, Folder 4)
      - Boletin de la Sociedad Mexicana de Geografia y Estadistica,9-12/45, Accession no. M0223 (Box 76, Folder 5)
      - Binder - S. 693, defining powers of the Secretary of the Interior with respect to the Colorado River under the Treaty with Mexico, Accession no. M0223 (Box 76, Folder 6)
      - Bill, Accession no. M0223 (Box 76, Folder 6)
      - Department Reports, Accession no. M0223 (Box 76, Folder 6)
      - Committee Reports, Accession no. M0223 (Box 76, Folder 6)
      - Memoranda, Accession no. M0223 (Box 76, Folder 6)
      - Miscellaneous, Accession no. M0223 (Box 76, Folder 6)
      - Water Treaty - Mexican Ratification proceedings from Mexican newspapers, Accession no. M0223 (Box 76, Folder 7)
      - Minutes, International Boundary and Water Commission with Imperial Irrigation District Comment - United States and Mexico Pertaming to the Colorado River, Accession no. M0223; (some pages missing) (Box 77, Folder 1)
      - Minutes, International Boundary and Water Commission with Imperial Irrigation District Comment - United States and Mexico Pertaming to the Colorado River, with accompanying TLS, 1/8/57, C. E. Corker to R.L. McCarty, Accession no. M0223; complete copy (Box 77, Folder 2)
      - Congressional Debates - Mexican Treaty, Accession no. M0223 (Box 77, Folder 3)
      - "Who Oppose the Mexican Water Treaty? The Senate Should Know Opposition to the Treaty is Nationwide" - issued by the Colorado River Water Users' Conference, Accession no. M0223 (Box 77, Folder 4)
      - Proposed Treaty - United States and Mexico - Colorado, Tijuana and Rio Grande Rivers - some points against the proposed treaty pending before the United States Senate, Accession no. M0223 (Box 77, Folder 5)
      - Excerpts from Treaty hearings for Mr. Scattergood re: proposition for Mexico in 1906 Rio Grande Treaty, Accession no. M0223 (Box 77, Folder 6)
      - Miscellaneous notes, Accession no. M0223; 2 pages (Box 77, Folder 7)
      - Folder of typed notes and excerpts on the Colorado River, Accession no. M0223 (Box 77, Folder 8)
      - Born to the Desert, by C. R. Richwood, Accession no. M0223 (Box 77, Folder 9)
      - Memoranda on Behalf of the Commission of 14 of the 7 Colorado River Basin States, Accession no. M0223 (Box 77, Folder 10)
      - Treaty of February 3, 194? - Spanish text and Mexican unofficial Statements, Accession no. M0223 (Box 77, Folder 11)
      - Memorandum - U. S. Need Not Fear Loss of Colorado River Water If Mexico Appeals For Arbitration Under 1929 Treaty, Accession no. M0223 (Box 78, Folder 1)
      - Statement on Behald of California Summarizing Some of the Reasons For Opposition to Proposed Treaty with Mexico Relating to the Colorado River, 3/20/44, Accession no. M0223 (Box 78, Folder 2)
      - News Item from Safford, Arizona Guardiari, 3/24/44 - "Defeat of Mexican Water Treaty Asked by Engineer" - original tearsheet and mimeo copy, Accession no. M0223 (Box 78, Folder 3)
      - Statement Respecting Proposed Treaty with Mexico Involving the Waters of the Colorado River, the Tijuana River and the Boundary Section of the Rio Grande, Accession no. M0223 (Box 78, Folder 4)
      - The Salt River Project, Arizona and the Mexican Colorado River Treaty, 3/5/46, Accession no. M0223 (Box 78, Folder 5)
      - Binder - legislative -history of the Mexican Water Treaty Bill, Accession no. M0223 (Box 78, Folder 6)
      - Tearsheet - Pacific Coast Edition of the Wall Street Journal, 3/l2/45, "United States and Mexico Plan a Big Public Works Program on the Border; Our Cost $167 Million", Accession no. M0223 (Box 78, Folder 7)
      - Mexican Water Treaty - Excerpts from Testimony Before the Senate Foreign Relations Committee In Answer to 10 Arguments Made by Proponents of the Treaty, 3/12/45, Accession no. M0223 (Box 78, Folder 8)
      - Memoranda - Excerpts Relating to the Treaty Between 'the United States and Mexico Regarding the Utilization of the Waters of the Rio Grande, Tijuana and Colorado Rivers and Bibliography of and References to Documents From Which Excerpts Are Taken, Accession no. M0223 (Box 78, Folder 9)
      - TL photocopy, 3/31/45, ? to Pat McCarran re: enclosing statement answering questions, with original questions, Accession no. M0223 (Box 78, Folder 10)
    - Sub-subseries 11. Upper Colorado River Storage Project And Compact
      - Memorandum on Why a High Dam at Some Point on the Lower Colorado is Needed by the Upper Basin and by the City of Denver, by L. Ward Bennister, Accession no. M0223 (Box 79, Folder 1)
      - Suggestions of the Governors of the Upper Basin for Lower Basin Compact, 8/30/27, Accession no. M0223 (Box 79, Folder 2)
      - Extract from mimeograph memorandum by Francis C. Wilson, Interstate River Commissioner for New Mexico, submitted to the Upper Basin States, Accession no. M0223 (Box 79, Folder 3)
      - "Pact Criticism is Largely on What It Does Not Say" - Statement of R. E. Sloan, Legal Adviser to the Arizona Commissioner, Accession no. M0223 (Box 79, Folder 4)
      - "The Upper Colorado Reclamation Project - Pro by Senator Arthur V. Watkins, Con by Raymond Moley", Accession no. M0223 (Box 79, Folder 4)
      - 2 pamphlets - "Big Dam Foolishmess" and "The Last Drop", Accession no. M0223 (Box 79, Folder 5)
      - U. S. Newspapers on guard... and See What This will Cost... It's Your Money, Accession no. M0223; 2 posters (Box 79, Folder 6)
      - Xerox, Report #270, 81st Congress, 1st Session, H.R. Granting Consent of the United States to the Upper Colorado River Basin Compact, Accession no. M0223 (Box 79, Folder 7)
      - Upper Colorado River Development Report Approved by Secretary Chapman, Accession no. M0223 (Box 79, Folder 8)
      - Storage Below the State of Colorado is not the Answer, Accession no. M0223 (Box 79, Folder 9)
      - Governor Johnson of Colorado Puts Some Cards on the Table, Accession no. M0223 (Box 79, Folder 10)
      - Hi Ho Aqualantes! - Statement by Rep. John P. Saybor, Penn., Accession no. M0223 (Box 79, Folder 11)
      - Plans for Huge Upper Colorado Dam Uncertain, Says Secretary McKay, Accession no. M0223 (Box 79, Folder 12)
      - Atomic Energy Progress Confronts Upper Colorado River Project with New Obstacle, Accession no. M0223 (Box 79, Folder 13)
      - Opposition to Upper Colorado River~Project, Accession no. M0223 (Box 79, Folder 14)
      - Why the Upper Colorado River Project is Against the Public Interest - Remarks of Hon. Paul H. Douglas, Accession no. M0223 (Box 79, Folder 15)
      - Bureau of Reclamation Economics Phoney as Three Dollar Bill, Accession no. M0223 (Box 79, Folder 16)
      - Reader'sDigest Reprint:"Dollars Into Dust" by Leslie A. Miller, Accession no. M0223 (Box 79, Folder 17)
      - Three articles by Craig Hosiner, Accession no. M0223 (Box 79, Folder 18)
      - Why Don't Private Power Companies Build the Upper Colorado River Project?, Accession no. M0223 (Box 79, Folder 19)
      - Bananas on Pike's Peak? 6/7/55, Accession no. M0223 (Box 79, Folder 20)
      - Bananas on Pike's Peak? 6/8/55, Accession no. M0223 (Box 79, Folder 21)
      - Release by Rep. John P. Saylor (Penn.) 6/9/55, Accession no. M0223 (Box 79, Folder 22)
      - Bananas on Pike's Peak? 6/11/55, Accession no. M0223; 4 different versions (Box 79, Folder 23)
      - Noted Scientist Calls for Impartial Board to Decide Upper Colorado Project Issues, Accession no. M0223 (Box 79, Folder 24)
      - Release by the Department of Water and Power 6/17/55, Accession no. M0223 (Box 79, Folder 25)
      - Bananas on Pike's Peak?6/17/55, Accession no. M0223 (Box 79, Folder 26)
      - California Taxpayers' Association Replies to Letter from Sen. Arthur V. Watkins, Accession no. M0223 (Box 79, Folder 27)
      - Bananas o.n Pike's Peak? - 2 versions, 6/23/55, Accession no. M0223 (Box 79, Folder 28)
      - Upper Colorado River Project Freez'es Up 323 Days a Year but Costs $5000 an Acre, Accession no. M0223 (Box 79, Folder 29)
      - The Outrage on General Taxpayers of Federal Reclamation, Accession no. M0223 (Box 79, Folder 30)
      - Notes to Mr. Robert L. McCarty re: your draft on Stratton-Sir- ' otkin Paper, 9/2/55, Accession no. M0223 (Box 79, Folder 31)
      - Comments on "The Echo Park Darn Controversy and Upper Colorado ' River Development" - original, Accession no. M0223 (Box 79, Folder 32)
      - Draft of comments on the Stratton~-Sirotkin Paper entitled "The Echo Park Dam Controversy and Upper Colorado River Development", Accession no. M0223 (Box 79, Folder 33)
      - Release by Rep. Craig Hosiner 10/24/55, Accession no. M0223 (Box 79, Folder 34)
      - Press release by Congressman William A. Dawson, Accession no. M0223 (Box 79, Folder 35)
      - Resolution of Colord.do River Board of California Opposing Pending Legislation Authorizing Colorado River Storage Pro- ject and Participating Projects, Accession no. M0223 (Box 79, Folder 36)
      - Release by Don J. Kinsey, 5/19/55, Accession no. M0223 (Box 79, Folder 37)
      - "Storage Below the State of Colorado is not the Aswer" by Ed C.Johnson, U. S. Senator - 40 congressional Record Scrapbook - articles, Accession no. M0223 (Box 79, Folder 39)
      - Releases from 8)4th Congress, 2nd Session, 1956, Accession no. M0223 (Box 79, Folder 42)
      - Upper Basin Projects, 1/59, Accession no. M0223 (Box 79, Folder 43)
      - Report t the Congress of the United States - Audit of Upper Colorado River Basin Water Resources Development Program, Bureau of Reclamation, Department of the Interior, Fiscal Years1957 - 1959, Accession no. M0223 (Box 79, Folder 44)
      - Leaflet - Bananas on Pike's Peak?, Accession no. M0223 (Box 79, Folder 45)
      - Enclosing notice for report by Colorado River Association, Accession no. M0223 (Box 79, Folder 46)
      - Memorandum for Mr. Ely from Mr. Allen re: Legislative History of Upper Colorado River Basin Compact, Accession no. M0223 (Box 79, Folder 47)
  - Subseries 4. Federal Water Power Act And Saline Conversion
    - Federal Water Power Act - Legislative and Legal History, Vol. I, Accession no. M0223 (Box 80, Folder 1)
      MS Division has negative microfilm
    - Federal Water Power Act - Legislative and Legal History, Vol. II, Accession no. M0223 (Box 80, Folder 2)
    - Federal Water Power Act - Legislative and Legal History, Vol. III, Accession no. M0223 (Box 80, Folder 3)
    - Federal Water Power Act - Legislative and Legal History, Vol. IV, Accession no. M0223 (Box 80, Folder 4)
    - Federal Water Power Act - Legislative and Legal History, Vol. V, Accession no. M0223 (Box 80, Folder 5)
    - Federal Water Power Act - Legislative and Legal History, Vol. VI, Accession no. M0223 (Box 80, Folder 6)
    - Federal Water Power Act - Legislative and Legal History, Vol. VII, Accession no. M0223 (Box 81, Folder 1)
    - Federal Water Power Act - Legislative and Legal History, Vol. VIII, Accession no. M0223 (Box 81, Folder 2)
    - Federal Water Power Act - Legislative and Legal History, Vol. IX, Accession no. M0223 (Box 81, Folder 3)
    - Federal Water Power Act - Legislative and Legal History, Vol. X, Accession no. M0223 (Box 81, Folder 4)
    - Federal Water Power Act - Legislative and Legal History, Vol. XI, Accession no. M0223 (Box 81, Folder 5)
    - Federal Water Power Act - Legislative and Legal History, Vol. XII, Accession no. M0223 (Box 81, Folder 6)
    - Federal Water Power Act - Legislative and Legal History, Vol. XIII-XV, Accession no. M0223 (Box 82, Folder 1)
    - Office of Saline Water - Suggested Types of Information Needed, Accession no. M0223 (Box 82, Folder 2)
    - TL mimeo, 1956, from David S. Jenkins re: enclosing report for "Saline Water ConversionReport for 1956", Accession no. M0223 (Box 82, Folder 3)
    - Memorandum, 2/25/58, C. Corker to N. Ely re: enclosing article from Engineering and Science, Accession no. M0223 (Box 82, Folder 4)
    - Article - "Desalting the Pacific" by Jack E. McKee, Accession no. M0223 (Box 82, Folder 5)
  - Subseries 5. Fryingpan - Arkansas Project Of Colorado
    - Reply to Questionnaire from John P. Saylor, M.C., to Secretary of the Interior re: H.R. 236, Accession no. M0223 (Box 83, Folder 1)
    - Fryingpan - Arkansas Project, 1953 - 1954, Accession no. M0223 (Box 83, Folder 2)
      Basic Documents and Supporting Data
    - Tearsheet - Newsweek, 5/24/54 - "Rube Goldberg in the Rockies" by Raymond Moley, Accession no. M0223 (Box 83, Folder 3)
    - Resolution of Colorado River Board of California Opposing Pending Legislation Authorizing Fryingpan - Arkansas Project in Colorado by Harold F. Pellegrin, 6/2/54, Accession no. M0223 (Box 83, Folder 4)
    - The Vote on the Fryingpan - Arkansas Project (H.R. 236) in the House of Representatives, Accession no. M0223 (Box 83, Folder 5)
      7/28/54
    - Supporting Documents and Data, Accession no. M0223 (Box 83, Folder 5)
    - House Hearings - Fryingpan - Arkansas, E.R. )4l2 - 3/55 - Statements of Ely and Matthew, Accession no. M0223 (Box 83, Folder 6)
    - Senate Hearings - Fryingpan - Arkansas, S. 300, 3/55 - Statements of Ely and Matthew, Accession no. M0223 (Box 83, Folder 6)
    - Fryingpan - Arkansas Project - 1955 Computations, Accession no. M0223 (Box 83, Folder 7)
    - Fryingpan - Arkansas Project 1955, Accession no. M0223 (Box 83, Folder 8)
    - Why the Upper Colorado River Basin and the Fryingpan - Arkansas Projects are Opposed - marked copy, Accession no. M0223 (Box 83, Folder 9)
  - Subseries 6. Ely, Sims Personal Correspondence
    - Personal Correspondence File - alphabetically arranged, Accession no. M0223 (Box 84, Folder 1)
    - File on Presidential Exemptions for Sims Ely's Mandatory Retirement at 65, Accession no. M0223 (Box 84, Folder 2)
    - Brown folder: personal papers and documents of Sims Ely, 1930 - 1945, Accession no. M0223 (Box 84, Folder 3)
      re: mine holdings, prospecting etc., ca. 150 items, letters, contracts, receipts, etc.
  - Subseries 7. Metropolitan Water District And Parker - Gila Project
    - Parker Dam Power Project - Contract for Installation and Use of Stepdown Transformers, Accession no. M0223 (Box 85, Folder 1)
    - Cooperative Contract for the Maintenance of Transmission Lines and Substation Facilities, Accession no. M0223 (Box 85, Folder 2)
    - Contract between the United States of America and the Tucson Gas, Electric Light and Power Co., Accession no. M0223 (Box 85, Folder 3)
    - TL carbon, 3/9/32, Ely to Dent reL supplementary water contract, Accession no. M0223 (Box 85, Folder 5)
    - Correspondence of ely and W. C. Mullendore, Southern California Edison Co., Ltd., Accession no. M0223 (Box 85, Folder 6)
    - 3 pgs. carbon from Parker Dam contract - Art. 15 - 16, Accession no. M0223 (Box 85, Folder 6)
    - Statement of energy delivered to City of Los Angeles during 6 months period, 12/1/39 - 5/31/40, Accession no. M0223 (Box 85, Folder 7)
    - Agreement between the Metropolitan Water District and Southern California and Salt River Valley. Water Users Association, Accession no. M0223 (Box 85, Folder 8)
    - Metropolitan Water District Finances - Correspondence, Accession no. M0223 (Box 85, Folder 9)
    - Material from Senate Hearings on 2nd Deficiency Appropriation Bill, Accession no. M0223 (Box 85, Folder 10)
    - Gila River Dam Statistics, Accession no. M0223 (Box 85, Folder 11)
    - TL carbon, 4/4/32, Ely to Commissioner Mead re: draft of cooperative contract for Parker Dam construction, Accession no. M0223 (Box 85, Folder 12)
    - Boulder Canyon Project - Cooperative contract for Construction and operation of Parker Dam, 4/l8/32, Accession no. M0223 (Box 85, Folder 13)
    - TN carbon, 3/17/32, Ely to F.E. Weymouth re: enclosing a letter, Accession no. M0223 (Box 85, Folder 14)
    - Memorandum, 5/12/32, J Henry Scattergood. to N. Ely re: proposed agreement between United States of America and Metropolitan Water District, Accession no. M0223 (Box 85, Folder 14)
    - TNS, 5/19/32, Ely to Scattergood re: Parker Dam, Accession no. M0223 (Box 85, Folder 15)
    - TL, 5/26/32, E. B. Debler to Porter J. Preston re: Parker - Gila Valley Diversion memorandum, Accession no. M0223 (Box 85, Folder 17)
    - Memorandum, 6/2/32, to McClellan re: allocation of power to be developed at proposed Parker Dam on the Colorado River, Accession no. M0223 (Box 85, Folder 18)
    - Memorandum, 1932, from A. V. Watkins re: power for irrigation pumping, Accession no. M0223 (Box 85, Folder 19)
    - Memorandum, 6/8/32, William S. Post to Commissioner re: Colorado River Indian Reservation, Accession no. M0223 (Box 85, Folder 20)
    - TL mimeo, 6/27/32, Ely to Secretary Wilbur re: draft of proposed contract for construction of Parker Dam, Accession no. M0223 (Box 85, Folder 21)
    - The Colorado River Aqueduct - prepared by the Metropolitan Water District of Southern California, 5/34, Accession no. M0223 (Box 85, Folder 22)
    - Draft of Art. 15 - Parker - Gila Project, Accession no. M0223 (Box 85, Folder 23)
    - Supplemental C9ntract for the Construction of Forebay and Power Plant Substructure at Parker Dam, 9/29/36, Accession no. M0223 (Box 85, Folder 24)
    - Extract from The Great Aqueduct, )4/bO/38 - "Need for Water" by C. C. Elder, Accession no. M0223 (Box 85, Folder 25)
    - The Great Aqueduct, by the Metropolitan Water District of Southern California, Accession no. M0223 (Box 85, Folder 26)
    - Parker Dam Power Project Contract, 3/18/41, Accession no. M0223 (Box 85, Folder 27)
    - Parker Dam Power Project - Memorandum of Understanding Covering the Sale of ElectMc Energy to the War Department, 12/13/42, Accession no. M0223 (Box 85, Folder 28)
    - Parker Dam Project - Memorandum of Understanding for Electric Service to Office of Indian Affairs for Colorado River Indian Reservation, 3/12/43, Accession no. M0223 (Box 85, Folder 29)
    - Parker Dam ' Project - Supplemental Contract for Sale of Electric Power and Energy to the California Electic Power Co., 3/30/43, Accession no. M0223 (Box 85, Folder 30)
    - Parker Dam Power Project - Contract for Electric Service for Arizona Lead. Company, 8/11/43, Accession no. M0223 (Box 85, Folder 31)
    - Parker Dam Power Project - Amedatory Contract between the United States of America and the Tucson Gas, Eleptric Light and Power Co., 9/17/142, Accession no. M0223 (Box 85, Folder 32)
    - Parker Dam Project, Accession no. M0223 (Box 85, Folder 33)
    - Parker Dam Power Project - Supplemental Memorandum of Understanding covering the Sale of Energy to the Office of Indian Affairs at Coolidge, Arizona, 12/15/44, Accession no. M0223 (Box 85, Folder 34)
    - Contract for Electric Service to Needles School District, Parker Dam Power Project, Accession no. M0223 (Box 85, Folder 35)
    - Parker Dam Power Project - Supplemental Contract for Sale of Electrical Power and Energy to Arizona Edison Co., Inc., Accession no. M0223 (Box 85, Folder 36)
    - Hearings Before the Commission on Irrigation and Reclamation -House of Representatives, 79th Congress, 2nd Session, on H.R. 5434 - a bill reauthorizing the Gila Federal Reclamation Project, etc., 7/18 - 22/46, Accession no. M0223 (Box 85, Folder 37)
    - Boulder Canyon Project, All American Canal, Coachella Valley Co. Water District - Contract for Construction of Distribution System and Drainage Works, Accession no. M0223 (Box 85, Folder 38)
    - Report on All American Canal Problems by William F. Kubach,7/25/50, Accession no. M0223 (Box 85, Folder 39)
    - Operation of the Imperial Dam - Pilot Knob Section of the All American Canal and Pilot Knob Power Development, Accession no. M0223 (Box 85, Folder 40)
    - H.R. 3790 - drafts, reports, hearings and committee prints, 82nd Congress, 1st Session, Accession no. M0223 (Box 85, Folder 41)
    - Release by Rep. John P. Saylor - "By Any Other Name Echo Park ' is the Same", 1/18/55, Accession no. M0223 (Box 85, Folder 42)
    - Senate Hearings for 1938 Appropriation for Gila Project, 1937, Accession no. M0223 (Box 85, Folder 43)
  - Subseries 8. Miscellaneous Pamphlets And Binders
    - Supplemental Materials in Evidence, by John B. Hurlburt, Accession no. M0223; 1 binder (Box 87)
    - Consumptive Use of Water for Agriculture, By Robert L. Lowry, Jr. and Arthur F. Johnson, Accession no. M0223 (Box 86, Folder 1)
    - Hearings Before a Subcommittee of the Committee on Commerce, U.S. Senate, 78th Congress, 2nd. Session, on H.R. 3961, Pt. 6,5/10 - 18/44, Accession no. M0223 (Box 86, Folder 2)
    - Hearings Before a Subcommittee of the Committee on Commerce, U.S. Senate, 78th Congress, 2nd. Session, on H.R. 4485, 5/29/44 - 6/15/44, Accession no. M0223 (Box 86, Folder 3)
    - Interstate Cooperation: A Study of the Interstate Compact, by Vincent V. Thursley, Accession no. M0223 (Box 86, Folder 5)
    - The PermanentDiversion Problem - Palo Verde District, Blythe, California, 5/54, Accession no. M0223 (Box 86, Folder 6)
    - First Interim Report - Advisory Committee on Weather Control, Washington, D. C., 2/56, Accession no. M0223 (Box 86, Folder 7)
    - Water Rights and Federalism - the Western Water Rights Settlement Bill of l95~ by Charles E. Corker, Accession no. M0223 (Box 86, Folder 8)
    - Petroleum Legislation the Underlying Realities, Accession no. M0223 (Box 86, Folder 9)
    - The Origins and. Policy Issues of the Pacific Southwest Water Plan, by Ernest A. Engelbert, Accession no. M0223 (Box 86, Folder 10)
    - Federal' Indian Water Rights: a Retrogressiqn to Quasi-Riparianism, Accession no. M0223 (Box 86, Folder 11)
    - A Pyrrhic Victory at Foley Square: the 2nd Circuit and Sabbatino, by Richard B. Liflich, Accession no. M0223 (Box 86, Folder 12)
    - Herbert Hoover - Public Positions and Honors, 7/64, Accession no. M0223 (Box 86, Folder 13)
    - How Can America Best Provide Food and Fiber for its Future Population - A Study in Fact, by Hon. John P. Saylor, Accession no. M0223 (Box 86, Folder 14)
    - Index - Hearings, House Committee on Irrigation of Arid Lands, 67th Congress, 2nd Session, on H. 11449, 1922 - 1923, Accession no. M0223 (Box 88, Folder 1)
    - TNS, 8/3/32 Ely to Ray Lyman Wilbur re: Parker Dam contract, Accession no. M0223 (Box 88, Folder 2)
    - In the District Court of Appeal, Second Appellate District, State of California, Division 2 - Stevens Drilling Company, Ltd. vs. Suprerior Court of the State of California - Answer to Application for Stay of Proceedings 9/3/36, Accession no. M0223 (Box 88, Folder 3)
    - 3 lists of names and addresses for mailing copies of papers or documents which may be submitted to R. V. L. Wright Special Representative, Accession no. M0223 (Box 88, Folder 4)
    - Agricultural Production in Northern Colorado Water Conservancy District as Related to National Defense, by E. H. Dyer and R. Barkley 12/41, Accession no. M0223 (Box 88, Folder 5)
    - Analysis of Power Features of Colorado - Big Thompson Project with Recommended Construction Schedule, By R. J. Tipton rev. 1/5/42, Accession no. M0223 (Box 88, Folder 6)
    - M.V.A. - an Address Delivered by C. Petrus Peterson before the Nebraska Reclamation Association 1/20/45, Accession no. M0223 (Box 88, Folder 7)